<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio</title>
    <link>/portfolio-2018/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio-2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lumi Mirror</title>
      <link>/portfolio-2018/work/lumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio-2018/work/lumi/</guid>
      <description>Senior Capstone  10 Weeks to Build a Real World Software Project    As part of the Stanford computer science major, all seniors have to spend 10 weeks building a significantly sized software project for their senior capstone. We would be evaluated on our ability to work cohesively as a team (peer reviews), individual code contributions (github review), and the project’s level of execution and completion (project fair).  Our team of 4 built the software and assembled the hardware behind Lumi, a gesture-controlled smart mirror that plays music, takes photos, and displays glanceable information like the time, the weather, and your twitter feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chair Shelf</title>
      <link>/portfolio-2018/side-projects/chair-shelf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio-2018/side-projects/chair-shelf/</guid>
      <description>Design is Problem Finding  Does the World Need Another Chair?    “Does the world really need another chair?” This was the question my ME 203: Design and Manufacturing professor asked me after I showed him my list of final project ideas. Every year he said chairs were built in his class and as I would later learn, were sort of obsessed over in the design world. Still, he encouraged me to build a chair but challenged me to build a chair that the world needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily UI</title>
      <link>/portfolio-2018/side-projects/daily-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio-2018/side-projects/daily-ui/</guid>
      <description>Daiy UI Challenge  Designing a UI Everyday for 100 Days    The Daily UI Challenge was a fun way to create something everyday. I wanted to use this challenge as an opportunity to improve my visual design skills and experiment with various new animation and prototyping tools.  This project is still in progress and if you&#39;re interested in following along, checkout my Daily UI Instagram, @jonyandesign.      PREVIOUS Chair Shelf    NEXT Lumi Mirror       </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ASES Rebrand</title>
      <link>/portfolio-2018/work/ases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio-2018/work/ases/</guid>
      <description>The Problem  An Outdated Brand Hurts Membership    The Asia-Pacific Student Entrepreneurship Society (ASES) was founded at Stanford University in 1998 with the mission of connecting entrepreneurs between Asia and Stanford. Since then, ASES has grown rapidly, spreading to over a dozen countries and gaining significant prestige, especially internationally. As a result of this international growth, ASES’s core mission has changed, becoming more about connecting entrepreneurs globally, and not just between Asia and Stanford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firsthand Delivery</title>
      <link>/portfolio-2018/work/firsthand/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio-2018/work/firsthand/</guid>
      <description>Background    On-demand food and grocery delivery startups have taken off in the last several years. However, on-demand retail delivery still seems to be almost non-existent. Firsthand Delivery was a pivot of a startup I founded in 2017 that attempts to test the value proposition of a retail delivery service. My co-founder and I gave ourselves a strict timeline of 4 weeks to build and launch a barebones MVP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/portfolio-2018/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio-2018/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/portfolio-2018/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio-2018/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>